Inventory of the Slavic Book Dealer Catalogs
Department of Special Collections
Slavic Book Dealer Catalogs
circa 1900-2009
M0471
Zalewski, Wojciech
Rondestvedt, Karen
20 linear feet 86 manuscript boxes
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
The collection features mostly printed and typewritten catalogs, price lists, press releases, and other materials (business correspondence, clippings, financial documents, newsletters, various publications, notes, misc.) related to the Slavic book trade in the Western world in the 20th - the beginning of the 21st centuries. Particularly beginning in late 1980s, the collection also includes catalogs and lists from dealers and other entities inside the Soviet Union, Russia, and Eastern and East-Central Europe seeking to sell material to Western libraries. The collection includes materials in almost all major Slavic languages (Russian, Polish, Ukrainian, Czech, etc.), as well as in English, French, German, and other Western and Central European languages.
Access
Collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use.
Acquisition Information
The collection was given incrementally between June 1988 and April 2009. It was formed by Wojciech Zalewski, curator for Slavic and Eastern European collections, Stanford University Libraries, and continued by Karen Rondestvedt, his successor.
Accession numbers: 1988-021, 1989-185, 1992-055, 1995-202, 1997-274, 1998-186, 2006-243.
Scope and Content of Collection
Printed and typewritten catalogs, price lists, press releases, and other materials (business correspondence, clippings, financial documents, newsletters, various publications, notes, misc.) related to the Slavic book trade in the Western world in the 20th - the beginning of the 21st centuries.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Booksellers and bookselling; Slavic imprints; Antiquarian booksellers - Catalogs; Europe, Eastern - Imprints; Russians - Foreign countries - History - Sources; Russian imprints - Foreign countries
Container List
- !Productive Arts!, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Contains 2 catalogs and 2 postcards. Multilingual.
- XLIX Antikvarno-bukinisticheskii auktsion "LG", 02.03.2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Contains a catalog with an attached handwritten note. In Russian.
- AARDM (Archives of Americans of Russian Descent in Minnesota), n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Contains a typewritten catalog with handwritten marks / notes / corrections, 1 page, slightly damaged. In Russian.
- ABRIS Publishing House, Autumn 1996 - Spring 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Contains a catalog. In Ukrainian, English, and Russian.
- Academia Publishing House of the Czechoslovak Academy of Sciences, April - June 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Contains a catalog. Multilingual.
- Academic International Press, 1973-1976; 1986; 1988-1990; 1992-1996; 1998-2000; n.d. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Contains catalogs, leaflets, and a small poster; 22 items total (including doubles). Multilingual.
- Access Russia, Inc., 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Contains a catalog and a folder with materials (2 business cards; a pocket calendar; a leaflet; a newsletter; a postcard; a business letter, 2 typewritten pages; handouts, 4 pages; a fragment of an article [?], 3 typewritten pages, slightly damaged). In Russian and English.
- Adamiak, Richard, 01.1.1980; n.d. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Contains a typewritten letter from R.Adamiak to W.Zalewski with numerous handwritten marks, 1 page; 2 typewritten catalogs, "Polonica and Polish-Americana", 8 pages total; an unopened posted envelope with handwritten notes. Some materials are damaged. In English and Polish.
- Adresář knižní kultury v ČSR, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Contains a catalog in Czech, with handwritten notes / marks on the front cover and inside.
- Academia teologii katolickiej, Warszawa, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Contains two catalogs in Polish.
- Akademichno izdatelstvo "Prof. Marin Drinov", Sofia, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Contains two catalogs in Bulgarian.
- Akademický antikvariát, Praha (Prague), 1992; n.d. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Contains a catalog, an order form and a handout, 1 page. In Czech.
- Akadémiai kiadó, Budapest [1 of 2], 1974; 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Contains four catalogs, some with handwritten notes / marks, slightly damaged. In Hungarian, English, and other languages.
- Akadémiai kiadó, Budapest [2 of 2], 1993; 2000; n.d. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Contains three catalogs and two typewritten price lists, 2 pages total, some with handwritten marks. In Hungarian, English, and other languages.
- Akademisk Boghandel, Denmark [1 of 2], 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Contains seven catalogs, some with handwritten notes / marks. In Russian, English, and other languages.
- Akademisk Boghandel, Denmark [2 of 2], 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Contains seven catalogs, in Russian and English mostly.
- Aktsiia Ltd., 10.25.1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Contains a catalog in Russian.
- Aleph-Bet Books, New York, 11.15-17.1985; n.d. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Contains a catalog and two postcards.
- Alexandrovicz, Stanislaw, Prof., July 2002; n.d. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Contains 2 printouts of e-mail letters from Karen Rondestvedt to Maciej Siekierski and vice versa, 2 pages, and a typewritten catalog with handwritten notes / marks (probably a printout), with titles in Russian and broken Ukrainian, 72 pages.
- Alexeieff, Alexandre, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Contains a typewritten letter from John W. Wronoski to Annette Keogh, 1 page, and a brochure "The Archive of the Estate of Alexandre Alexieff" by "Lame Duck Books".
- Alt, Johannes, Booksellers, Germany, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Contains a catalog, in English and German mostly. Slightly damaged.
- Altenberger Books International, MA, 11 15 1993 - 1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Contains catalogs and related correspondence, 57 typewritten pages total. (One letter with a handwritten note from Alicja Altenberger to Wojciech Zalewski, in Polish.) In Polish and English.
- Am Rhein, Buchantiquariat, 1997 [?] (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Contains a catalog in Czech, German, English, and other languages.
- Amco Press, 1997 [?] (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Contains a catalog, a flyer, and a letter with a handwritten signature and two handwritten notes / corrections, 8 pages total. In Romanian, English, French, and other languages.
- American Book Auction Catalogues, 09.14.1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Contains one printout (1 page) with numerous handwritten notes / corrections; damaged.
- American Institute of Polish Culture of Miami, Florida, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Contains a catalog, a flyer, a letter, and a photocopy of a clipping. In Polish and English.
- American-Russian Trade Company, 02.28.1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Contains a catalog and a separate order form, 1 page. Slightly damaged.
- Andrigal Ltd., 07.22.1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Contains an e-mail printout, 5 pages total, with a handwritten addition. Slightly damaged.
- ANSO, Novosibirsk (Russia) [1 of 2], 1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Contains catalogs (4 typewritten catalogs, 37 pages total, and a brochure). In Russian and English.
- ANSO, Novosibirsk (Russia) [2 of 2], 1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Contains catalogs (4 typewritten catalogs, 95 pages total, and a brochure). In Russian.
- Antiquariat Bergische Bücherstube, July 1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Contains a catalog with a handwritten note on the front cover. In German and English.
- Antiquariat Kiepert GmbH, Berlin, 07.23.1993; n.d. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Contains a brochure with an enclosure and a typewritten letter (with a handwritten signature), 1 page. In German and English.
- Antiquariat Seidel and Richter, Berlin, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Contains a catalog with handwritten marks / notes. In German.
- Antykwariat Lamus, 11.05.1994-06.15.1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Contains two catalogs with enclosed order forms, one with several handwritten notes / marks, slightly damaged. In Polish.
- Antykwariat Naukowy, Poznan (Poland) [1 of 3], 1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Contains a catalog, damaged. In Polish and German mostly.
- Antykwariat Naukowy, Poznan (Poland) [2 of 3], 1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Contains a catalog, in Polish and German mostly.
- Antykwariat Naukowy, Poznan (Poland) [3 of 3], 1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Contains two catalogs with enclosed postcards. In Polish, French, and German mostly.
- Antykwariat Wspolczesny / "Polish Antiquarian Books", Dec. 1996 - Jan 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Contains 3 catalogs with enclosed order forms. In Polish mostly.
- Apka Publishers, Translators and Book Distributors, Winter 1993 - Summer / Fall 1999; n.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Contains 3 catalogs (including doubles), a leaflet, 3 flyers / photocopies. In Russian and English.
- Apollo Book Co., Ltd., 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Contains a price list in Mongolian and English, 1 page.
- Archaeology, Ethnology and Anthropology of Eurasia, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Contains a newsletter with two handwritten notes on the front cover.
- (The) Archives of Non-Traditional Press / "The Archives of the Independent Press", 1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Contains 3 catalogs (two typewritten catalogs, 26 pages total, and a brochure), a typewritten related letter, 1 page, and a photocopy of a part of the brochure with several attachments. All materials with handwritten notes / marks. Slightly damaged. In Russian and English.
- ARDIS, 1974/1975 - 1996 [?]; 2006 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Contains catalogs and newsletters, 8 items total, some incomplete and / or damaged. In Russian and English.
- ARKADY Publishing House, Poland, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Contains a newsletter with 2 enclosed pages (a letter and a flyer).
- Ark's Intervideo, California, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Contains a handmade brochure.
- ARMARIUM, Germany [1 of 2], Sept 1984 - Oct 1986; n.d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Contains 5 catalogs, some with handwritten notes / marks. In German and Czech mostly.
- ARMARIUM, Germany [2 of 2], Nov 1987 - June 1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Contains 5 catalogs (including doubles), one with an enclosure; some with handwritten notes / marks. In German and Czech mostly.
- Arno Press, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Contains 2 catalogs, one with numerous handwritten additions, marks, and notes. Slightly damaged.
- Ars Polona, Poland [1 of 3], 1980; 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Contains 5 catalogs (including doubles, one with an enclosed flyer), one with a handwritten note on the front cover. In Polish and English.
- Ars Polona, Poland [2 of 3], 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Contains 3 catalogs. In Polish and English.
- Ars Polona, Poland [3 of 3], 2000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Contains 2 typewritten supplements to a general price list and to a list of periodicals, 18 pages total, and an official typewritten letter (with a handwritten signature), 1 page. Incl. also a catalog, slightly damaged. In Polish and English.
- Artefakt, Bulgaria, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Contains a flyer / order form. In Bulgarian.
- ASEEPL - A Bibliographical Guide on the Soviet Union and Eastern Europe, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Contains a leaflet.
- Asian Rare Books Inc. (New York), July 1, 1986; n.d. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Contains a typewritten price list, two flyers and related materials.
- Astra Press, England, 1989-1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Contains 7 catalogs (including doubles, some with flyers / library cards enclosed), some with handwritten marks / notes. Some are slightly damaged.
- ATC Books International, Inc. [1 of 2], 1997 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Contains 4 catalogs, some are slightly damaged. In Polish.
- ATC Books International, Inc. [2 of 2], 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Contains 6 catalogs, some with handwritten notes; in Polish.
- Atlantis Books, March 21, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Contains one catalog.
- Aulos, The Publishing House (Prague), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Contains a catalog with a handwritten note on the front cover. In Czech and English.
- The Austin Book Shop, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Contains a catalog, slightly damaged. In English and Polish mostly.
- L'Autodidacte-Librairie, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Contains a catalog with several handwritten notes on the front cover and with a flyer enclosed. In French, English, and German mostly.
- AVE Religious Store, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Contains a completed questionnaire, 1 page.
- AVIS (Belgrade, Yugoslavia), 1997 - 06.25.1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Contains a catalog with handwritten notes, a handwritten note from M.S. to W[ojciech] Z[alewski], 1 page, and two identical book offers, 2 pages. In English and Serbo-Croatian.
- The Backlist, May 1994 - Nov 1998 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Contains 4 catalogs, some are slightly damaged.
- Bavin, S.P., Gurbolikova, A., "Knigi, kotorye chitaiut vse: bibliograficheskie ocherki", 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Contains a book and a typewritten note (the information about the book). Slightly damaged.
- Bayda Books (Australia), 07.14.1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Contains a typewritten letter, 1 page.
- Belarusan Institute of Arts and Sciences, 07.04.1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Contains a release, 1 typewritten page with handwritten notes.
- Belaruskaia navuka (Minsk, Belarus'), 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Contains 2 catalogs. In Byelorussian and Russian.
- Beloglazov, Konstantin, April 1996 - Oct 1997 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Contains e-mail printouts, 6 items total, heavily annotated. In English and Russian (in Latin transliteration) mostly.
- Benjamins, John, Antiquariat B.V., Oct 11, 1979-1980; n.d. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Contains 2 catalogs (2 copies of the same issue, one copy is heavily annotated), in English, Czech, Polish, and French mostly, and a typewritten questionnaire with handwritten notes / marks, 1 page.
- Berkeley Slavic Specialties, Winter 1995 - Winter 1999; n.d. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Contains 10 catalogs total (including doubles), some with numerous handwritten notes / marks etc.
- Bernett, F.A., Inc., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Contains 2 catalogs (one typewritten, with a business card attached, and one printed).
- Bibliographien zur Geschichte und Landeskunde Ostmitteleeuropas, 1985-04.07.1999 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Contains a book with a handwritten dedication from Horst [von Chmielewski] to Wojciech Zalewski; a photocopy of an off print from another book (a poem by Jan Twardowski), 1 page; a record for the book, 1 page; "form selections" and notification slips, 11 items, with a handwritten note attached.
- Biblionne, 06.02.2006 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Contains a catalog (a Web printout), 5 pages, the last part is slightly damaged. In Russian.
- Biblioteka Centrala de Stat, Romania, 12.05-08.1980 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Contains a letter / catalog, 3 pages, with handwritten notes / marks, a typewritten note from Marguerite Studemeister to Wojciech Zalewski, with handwritten additions, 1 page. Multilingual, damaged. Incl. also catalog with numerous handwritten additions / corrections / marks, in Romanian, French, and English mostly; damaged.
- Biblioteca Central? Universitar? (Romania), n.d. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Contains a typewritten letter with a handwritten [?] signature and a stamp, 1 page, in French, and a catalog, 9 pages, in English, French, and Italian [?] mostly.
- Biblioteka G?ówna UAM (Poland), 1967-1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Contains a catalog and a supplement to another catalog (with a handwritten note on the first page), in Polish. Incl. also a business card in Czech.
- Biblioteka Uniwersytecka w Warszawie, Poland, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Contains a microfilms catalog, slightly damaged. In Polish, French, German and Russian (in Latin transliteration) mostly.
- Big Ben Books, 05.15.1967-01.07.1987; n.d. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Contains photocopies of clippings (8 items); 2 photocopies of articles about Stanley W. Zamonski in "Who's Who in the West" and "Personalities in America" (2 items); 2 blank order forms; a flyer with an order form; a dust jacket of the book "The '59ers: Roaring Denver in the Gold Rush Days" by Stanley W. Zamonski and Teddy Keller; a typewritten questionnaire with handwritten answers; photocopies of letters from Gene M. Gressley to Stanley W. Zamonski and vice versa; a typewritten letter from Wojciech Zalewski to Stanley W. Zamonski; a handwritten letter from Stanley W. Zamonski to Wojciech Zalewski.
- Blane Hörner Verlag, Bernd E. Scholz, Nov. 1990 [?] (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Contains a catalog (probably a photocopy), a cover is missing; damaged. In English, Russian (both original and Latin transliteration), and German mostly.
- BMS, 12.23.1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Contains a typewritten catalog, 8 pages, with a typewritten note attached; slightly damaged. In French, Serbo-Croatian and other languages.
- Bohemia Books U.S.A., 01.11.1993; n.d. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Contains a catalog and a price list. In English and Czech.
- Lucie Bolduc Inc., March 1978-01.25.1983; n.d. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Contains typewritten catalogs / price lists, mostly annotated, and related correspondence, 13 items total, some are damaged. In English, Polish and Russian (in Latin transliteration) mostly.
- BONOT Enterprises [1 of 4], 06.01.1994-04.01.1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Contains 3 catalogs, typewritten, with a few handwritten marks, slightly damaged. In Ukrainian (in Latin transliteration) and English.
- BONOT Enterprises [2 of 4], 10.01.1995-08.01.1996 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- BONOT Enterprises [3 of 4], 11.01.1996-02.01.1998 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Contains 3 typewritten catalogs / price lists, slightly damaged. In Ukrainian (in Latin transliteration) and English.
- . "BONOT Enterprises" [4 of 4], 06.01.1998-11.01.1999 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Book Castle, Inc., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Contains a catalog.
- The Book Connection, 03.12.1987; n.d. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Contains a typewritten catalog / price list (in Russian) and a typewritten letter from Neil Burnett to Library Acquisitions Department, 1 page.
- Book World Prague, 5th International Book Fair, 05.20-23.1999 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Contains a program of the fair, in Czech and English.
- Books and Art in the USSR, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Contains 3 catalogs with a few handwritten notes, slightly damaged.
- Book For Us, 11.30.1991-04.11.1994; n.d. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Contains 3 catalogs / price lists (one typewritten, two brochures) and related business correspondence, 5 items. All documents with numerous handwritten marks / additions / corrections. In Russian, English, and Latvian. Some items are slightly damaged.
- Books From the Czech Republic, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  Contains a catalog with a handwritten note. In Czech, German, and English.
- Books Poland, 07.05-08.06.1999; n.d. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Contains a catalog and related correspondence, including e-mail printouts (7 pages total). In English and Polish.
- Books Trade and Services, 11.15.1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Contains a catalog in Serbo-Croatian and a letter in English (typewritten, 1 page). Slightly damaged.
- Bookstores in the Toronto Area, by Mary Stevens and Zelimirka Mastic-Levi, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Contains a catalog with an attached note and a business card.
- Bradda Books Ltd., 1972; 1974; Jan. 1978; n.d. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Contains 2 catalogs (one with handwritten marks / notes), a leaflet and a book request form (filled out). In Russian and English.
- Brannan Books, 04.17.1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Contains a typewritten letter (with numerous handwritten notes) from Paul Brannan to Wojciech Zalewski, 1 page; a photocopy of a page from a price list / catalog (with numerous handwritten notes); a blue catalog [?] card with "Brannan Books" business address; and a photocopy of a page from a book (in Russian). Slightly damaged.
- Brandywine Books, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Contains a catalog, multilingual.
- E. J. Brill, Ltd. [1 of 4], June 1979; n.d. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Contains 2 catalogs with numerous handwritten marks / notes.
- E. J. Brill, Ltd. [2 of 4], July 1980-May 1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Contains 3 catalogs, multilingual.
- E. J. Brill, Ltd. [3 of 4], Feb-April 1987 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Contains 3 catalogs, multilingual, 2 of them being copies of the same issue.
- E. J. Brill, Ltd. [4 of 4], Oct 1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Contains a catalog with numerous handwritten marks / notes, slightly damaged.
- The British Library, A Catalog of Russian Avant-Garde Books, 1912-1934 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Contains a photocopy with handwritten marks / additions, pages 102-110 and a title page.
- Bronze Horseman Literary Agency, 1995-06.24.2002 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Contains 5 catalogs (including doubles) in Russian and English, some with handwritten notes / marks, slightly damaged; one typewritten catalog, 13 pages; related correspondence, 5 pages.
- Brücken Verlag, 1983-1985/86 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Contains 2 catalogs and related correspondence, 1 page. In German and Russian (in Latin transliteration) mostly.
- BTS-Book, Trade and Services, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Contains 3 catalogs, some with handwritten notes / marks, in English, Serbo-Croatian, and German mostly.
- Buchhandlung SOI, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  Contains a catalog in English and Russian (in Latin transliteration).
- Buchversand Krieger, 04.14.1998 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  Contain a typewritten catalog, 4 pages, in English and Russian (in Latin transliteration).
- Bulanin, Dmitrii [1 of 2], 1993/94-1999 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Contains 4 catalogs, in English and Russian mostly, and a business card.
- Bulanin, Dmitrii [2 of 2], 03.12.1993-08.30.2006 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Contains numerous e-mail printouts / catalogs, in English and Russian (in Latin transliteration).
- Bulgarian Books, 1996-2004; n.d. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Contains 3 catalogs, a typewritten content list / letter, 20 pages, and an e-mail printout / catalog; in English and Bulgarian (in Latin transliteration).
- Burke, J., Antiquarian and Foreign Bookseller, Nov. 15, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Contains a catalog with handwritten marks / notes, slightly damaged.
- Bücher, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Byelorussian Institute of arts and Sciences, Inc., 1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Contains a typewritten catalog, 13 pages, with handwritten additions / marks / corrections. In English and Byelorussian (in Latin transliteration).
- Byelorussian Periodicals, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Contains a leaflet with handwritten marks / corrections. In Russian, English, and Byelorussian. Slightly damaged.
- Califia Books, 1999-2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Contains 2 catalogs (one with a handwritten note on the front cover) and a postcard.
- Canadian Institute of Ukrainian Studies, 1993/1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Contains a catalog, in English and Ukrainian.
- Carpatho-Rusyn Research Center, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Contains a price list / order form and a typewritten catalog / price list, 3 pages. In Russian, Ukrainian, English, Czech, and Rusyn mostly.
- Central Books Ltd. (London), Autumn 1981; n.d. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Contains a leaflet / price list and an order form.
- Central Bureau of Statistics, Republic of Croatia, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Contains a brochure "Statistical information" in Serbo-Croatian and English.
- Central National Library "Djurdje Crnojevic", Cetinje, 1998-10.04 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  1999; n.d.
- Central Statistical Office (Poland), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Contains 2 brochures with the title "Editorial Title-Plan".
- Chadwyck-Healey Inc., Sept 30, 1993; n.d. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Contains a catalog, PR and related correspondence, 4 items.
- Chagano Books, April 29, 1987-Dec 1992 [?] (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Contains typewritten price lists / catalogs with handwritten additions / marks, 13 pages total. Some titles are in Russian (in Latin transliteration). Slightly damaged.
- Chalidze Publications, 1983-1985/1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)